Finding Aid for the Joseph Chouinard Collection of Images, circa 1928-2006
State University of New York at Buffalo. Music Library
- Smaller format photographs, circa 1928-circa 1981, III.; Item 070-200
  - Joseph Chouinard in costume for the character of the Imperial commissioner and unidentified woman in costume for performance of Puccini's Madame Butterfly by the Chattanooga Opera Association, 1955 November, 1 black and white photograph; Photographer: Unidentified Location: Chattanooga (Tenn.) Venue: Chattanooga High School (Chattanooga, Tenn.) (Box 1, Image 180)
  - Portrait of Joseph Chouinard, circa 1955, 1 black and white photograph; Photographer: Unidentified Location: Unknown location (Box 1, Image 181)
  - People in Western costumes, possibly cast members for a performance of Annie get your gun, circa 1957, 1 color photograph; Photographer: Mercure (Paris, France) Location: Unknown location On verso: Paris TV RDF (Box 1, Image 182)
  - New Arundel Opera Theatre postcard, circa 1958, 1 Card photographs; Photographer: Albrecht, Arthur Location: Kennebunkport (Me.) Venue: Arundel Opera Theatre (Kennebunkport, Me.) (Box 1, Image 183)
  - Joseph Chouinard (center) as Frank Butler in the Arundel Opera production of Annie get your gun, 1959 July 1, 1 black and white photograph; Photographer: Unidentified Location: Kennebunkport (Me.) Venue: Arundel Opera Theatre (Kennebunkport, Me.) (Box 1, Image 184)
  - Joseph Chouinard (center) in costume in the role of Bonze in Puccini's Madame Butterfly, presented by the Tri-Cities Opera Company, 1959 October, 1 black and white photograph; Photographer: Unidentified Location: Binghamton (N.Y.) Venue: Masonic Temple (Binghamton, N.Y.) (Box 1, Image 185)
  - Thomas Chouinard holding a basketball, 1960, 1 black and white photograph; Photographer: Fox Co. Location: Unknown location (Box 1, Image 186)
  - Joseph Chouinard holding a dog in his lap while sitting outside a house, 1961 June, 1 black and white photograph; Photographer: Unidentified Location: Unknown location (Box 1, Image 187)
  - Hopkins Center at Dartmouth College, Hanover, New Hampshire postcard, circa 1962, 1 color photograph; Photographer: Allen, Carleton Location: Hanover (N.H.) Venue: Hopkins Center (Box 1, Image 188)
  - Joseph Chouinard as the character Amos Murphy in a Tri-Cities Opera Workshop production of Myron S. Fink's Jeremiah, 1962 May, 1 black and white photograph; Photographer: Unidentified Location: Binghamton (N.Y.) Venue: Harpur College (Box 1, Image 189)
  - Joseph Chouinard as the character Brighella in a production of Salieri's The little harliquinade at the Florida International Music Festival, 1967 July, 1 color photograph; Photographer: Unidentified Location: Daytona Beach (Fla.) (Box 1, Image 190)
  - Joseph Chouinard holding a dog while sitting in San Bernardino, 1974 June, 1 color photograph; Photographer: Unidentified Location: San Bernardino (Calif.) On verso: Genuine Burgess photograph (Box 1, Image 191)
  - Joseph Chouinard sitting with the children of Lionel Pike, 1979 November, 1 color photograph; Photographer: Unidentified Location: Unknown location (Box 1, Image 192)
  - Joseph Chouinard standing by a door, 1981 June, 1 color photograph; Photographer: Unidentified Location: Unknown location (Box 1, Image 193)
  - Joseph Chouinard (2nd from right) sitting at a dinner table with four friends, circa 1981, 1 color photograph; Photographer: Unidentified Location: Unknown location (Box 1, Image 194)
  - Three friends of Joseph Chouinard standing in a living room, circa 1981, 1 color photograph; Photographer: Unidentified Location: Unknown location (Box 1, Image 195)
  - Joseph Chouinard holding a score or text while a woman plays the piano, circa 1981, 1 color photograph; Photographer: Unidentified Location: Unknown location (Box 1, Image 196)
  - Portrait of Joseph Chouinard, circa 1952, 1 black and white photograph; Photographer: Unidentified Location: Unknown location (Box 1, Image 197)
  - Passport portrait of Joseph Chouinard, 1961 May 18, 1 black and white photograph; Photographer: Unidentified Location: Unknown location (Box 1, Image 198)
  - Portrait of Joseph Chouinard, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Photographer: Unidentified Location: Unknown location (Box 1, Image 199)
  - Portrait of Joseph Chouinard, circa 1972, 1 black and white photograph; Photographer: Platte of Hollywood (Hollywood, Calif.) Location: Hollywood (Calif.) (Box 1, Image 200)
- Drawings, 1952-1953, IV.; Item 200-206
  - Caricature of conductor Hugh Ross, 1953, 1 drawn caricature; Artist: Adler, Wolf, 1924-2012 Location: Stockbridge (Mass.) Inscribed: To Joe with best wishes, Wolf Adler. On verso: caricature of Charles Munch (Box 1, Image 201)
  - Caricature of composer Carlos Chávez, 1953, 1 drawn caricature; Artist: Adler, Wolf, 1924-2012 Location: Stockbridge (Mass.) Inscription on verso: Carlos Chavez, Tanglewood 1953 by Wolf Adler. (Box 1, Image 202)
  - Caricature of conductor Charles Munch, 1953, 1 drawn caricature; Artist: Adler, Wolf, 1924-2012 Location: Stockbridge (Mass.) On verso: caricature of Hugh Ross (Box 1, Image 203)
  - Caricature of Joseph Chouinard, 1953, 1 drawn caricature; Artist: Adler, Wolf, 1924-2012 Location: Stockbridge (Mass.) On verso: caricature of Leonard Bernstein (Box 1, Image 204)
  - Caricature of Leonard Bernstein, 1953, 1 drawn caricature; Artist: Adler, Wolf, 1924-2012 Location: Stockbridge (Mass.) On verso: caricature of Joseph Chouinard (Box 1, Image 205)
  - Colored drawing of a female figure by P. Heck, 1952, 1 drawing; Artist: Heck, P. (Box 1, Image 206)
- 35 mm slides, 1954-February 1965, V.; Item 207-225
  - Joseph Chouinard holding a viola, 1954, 1 35 mm slide; Photographer: Unidentified Location: Unknown location (Box 1, Image 207)
  - Joseph Chouinard holding a viola, 1954, 1 35 mm slide; Photographer: Unidentified Location: Unknown location (Box 1, Image 208)
  - Joseph Chouinard holding a viola, 1954, 1 35 mm slide; Photographer: Unidentified Location: Unknown location (Box 1, Image 209)
  - Joseph Chouinard holding a viola, 1954, 1 35 mm slide; Photographer: Unidentified Location: Unknown location (Box 1, Image 210)
  - Joseph Chouinard holding a viola, 1954, 1 35 mm slide; Photographer: Unidentified Location: Unknown location (Box 1, Image 211)
  - Joseph Chouinard holding a viola, 1954, 1 35 mm slide; Photographer: Unidentified Location: Unknown location (Box 1, Image 212)
  - Joseph Chouinard holding a viola, 1954, 1 35 mm slide; Photographer: Unidentified Location: Unknown location (Box 1, Image 213)
  - Joseph Chouinard holding a viola, 1954, 1 35 mm slide; Photographer: Unidentified Location: Unknown location (Box 1, Image 214)
  - Possible unidentified production of Massenet's Don Quichotte, 1965 February, 1 35 mm slide; Photographer: Unidentified Location: Unknown location Note on slide carton: Feb. 1965 Don Quixotte (Box 1, Image 215)
  - Possible unidentified production of Massenet's Don Quichotte, 1965 February, 1 35 mm slide; Photographer: Unidentified Location: Unknown location Note on slide carton: Feb. 1965 Don Quixotte (Box 1, Image 216)
  - Possible unidentified production of Massenet's Don Quichotte, 1965 February, 1 35 mm slide; Photographer: Unidentified Location: Unknown location Note on slide carton: Feb. 1965 Don Quixotte (Box 1, Image 217)
  - Possible unidentified production of Massenet's Don Quichotte, 1965 February, 1 35 mm slide; Photographer: Unidentified Location: Unknown location Note on slide carton: Feb. 1965 Don Quixotte (Box 1, Image 218)
  - Possible unidentified production of Massenet's Don Quichotte?, 1965 February, 1 35 mm slide; Photographer: Unidentified Location: Unknown location Note on slide carton: Feb. 1965 Don Quixotte (Box 1, Image 219)
  - Possible unidentified production of Massenet's Don Quichotte, 1965 February, 1 35 mm slide; Photographer: Unidentified Location: Unknown location Note on slide carton: Feb. 1965 Don Quixotte (Box 1, Image 220)
  - Possible unidentified production of Massenet's Don Quichotte, 1965 February, 1 35 mm slide; Photographer: Unidentified Location: Unknown location Note on slide carton: Feb. 1965 Don Quixotte (Box 1, Image 221)
  - Possible unidentified production of Massenet's Don Quichotte, 1965 February, 1 35 mm slide; Photographer: Unidentified Location: Unknown location Note on slide carton: Feb. 1965 Don Quixotte (Box 1, Image 222)
  - Possible unidentified production of Massenet's Don Quichotte, 1965 February, 1 35 mm slide; Photographer: Unidentified Location: Unknown location Note on slide carton: Feb. 1965 Don Quixotte (Box 1, Image 223)
  - Possible unidentified production of Massenet's Don Quichotte, 1965 February, 1 35 mm slide; Photographer: Unidentified Location: Unknown location Note on slide carton: Feb. 1965 Don Quixotte (Box 1, Image 224)
  - Possible unidentified production of Massenet's Don Quichotte, 1965 February, 1 35 mm slide; Photographer: Unidentified Location: Unknown location Note on slide carton: Feb. 1965 Don Quixotte (Box 1, Image 225)
- Oversize, 1956, VI.; Item 226-227
  - Performance of Joseph Haydn's The Creation by the National Music Camp Festival Choir at the Interlochen Arts Camp, with University of Michigan Orchestra, Maynard Klein, conductor, 1956, 1 black and white photograph; Photographer: Unidentified Location: Interlochen (Mich.) Venue: Interlochen Center for the Arts (Box 2, Image 226)
  - Oil painting portrait of Joseph Chouinard as a young man, undated, 1 oil portrait; Artist: Unidentified (Oversize Framed art, Image 227)
Search Terms
The following terms have been used to index the description of this collection in the Library's online catalog.
Subjects
Musicians--Photographs; Okinawa-ken (Japan)--Photographs; World War, 1939-1945--Japan--Okinawa Island--Photographs; Pikes Peak (Colo.)--Photographs; Chouinard, Joseph Jerod, 1926-2014--Photographs
Genres
Photographs; Caricatures; Color slides
Associated Material
Related Resources
Related Resources in the Music Library
Joseph Chouinard Papers
Mus. Arc. 71.1
Contains 6 boxes of personal documents, correspondence, concert programs, and clippings.
Joseph Chouinard Collection of Scores
Mus. Arc. 71.3
Contains scores of 33 musical works by Joseph Chouinard.